Sorry, can't stop to talk now. I'm rushed
off my feet with this blooming banquet.
cue-2
Well, this won't be the last barrel of gin
I have to add to the punch. There hasn't
cue-3
been a proper election contest here since,
well, before I was born. They usually
cue-4
just come to an arrangement about which
MPs will represent us. Obvious why. If
cue-5
there's a proper election, all the voters
have to be bribed, and that's expensive.
cue-6
But that's exactly what's going on here,
an election entertainment. Free drink,
cue-7
free food for anyone promising to support
the new interest, as they call
cue-8
themselves.
cue-9
We had the old interest in here yesterday.
Most people call them the Tories. Look
cue-10
what they did to the painting of King
William. They really hate 'em.
cue-11
And it's the Whigs in today. Not much to
choose between them, if you ask me. Look
cue-12
around the table, a motley lot. Not all of
'em can vote, of course. I can't for one.
cue-13
But even when I'm older, I won't be rich
enough. Only about one in 20 can vote. No
cue-14
women, nobody under 21, and only those men
who own or rent property of sufficient
cue-15
value. Still, when there's an election,
everyone gets to play a part. If you're
cue-16
not in here gorging yourself to death,
maybe you're out in the town, marching
cue-17
through the streets, listening to the
speeches, singing ballads, or picking a
cue-18
fight. See T. Carter over there with his
bludgeon? Oh, he looks like he's been
cue-19
doing a good bit of persuading, though
he's taken a few blows himself. Voters or
cue-20
not, you can't say that these people don't
care about the election. Plus, there's
cue-21
all the money being spent. It's keeping
this inn in business. You should speak to
cue-22
one of the candidates maybe. You can
hardly notice them in all this commotion.
cue-23
They're the ones paying for it all. Look,
there they are, behind me, at the end of
cue-24
the table.